http://wfdu.fm/Whats-Happening/privacy%20policy/

Toggle navigation
Home
WFDU
WFDU HD2WFDU HD3WFDU on Internet RadioWFDU/FCC Public Inspection FileAboutManagementiPhone AppAndroid AppHistoryContact Us
Listen
Listen LiveiHeart RadioAlternate Listen LiveShow ArchivesPlaylistsAudio Now
Our Manatee - Margarito
FAN MAIL!
RADIO-ON-TV
WFDU Power Increase!
Highest Ratings!WFDU on Internet Radio!Privacy PolicyKudos From Listeners!
Money Matters
DonateWFDU 89 Club T-ShirtsWFDU Media KitUnderwritingUnderwriting Media Kit
Home
WFDU
WFDU HD2WFDU HD3WFDU on Internet RadioWFDU/FCC Public Inspection FileAboutManagementiPhone AppAndroid AppHistoryContact Us
Listen
Listen LiveiHeart RadioAlternate Listen LiveShow ArchivesPlaylistsAudio Now
Our Manatee - Margarito
FAN MAIL!
RADIO-ON-TV
WFDU Power Increase!
Highest Ratings!WFDU on Internet Radio!Privacy PolicyKudos From Listeners!
Money Matters
DonateWFDU 89 Club T-ShirtsWFDU Media KitUnderwritingUnderwriting Media Kit
Listen Live
Archives
Donate to WFDU
What's Happening
Highest Ratings!
WFDU on Internet Radio!
Privacy Policy
Kudos From Listeners!
Privacy Policy
WFDU Radio built the WFDU Radio app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by WFDU Radio at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at WFDU Radio unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection and Use
For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to None. The information that we request is will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.
The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.
Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app
Google Play Services
Log Data
We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device's internal memory.
This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.
Service Providers
We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
To facilitate our Service;
To provide the Service on our
behalf;
To perform Service-related
services; or
To assist us in analyzing how
our Service is used.
We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
Security
We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links to Other Sites
This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This privacy policy page was created at privacypolicytemplate.net and modified/generated by App Privacy Policy Generator
Bumper Stickers  | Privacy Policy  | Underwriting  |
Copyright © 2020
WFDU(FM) is owned and operated by Fairleigh Dickinson University
Latest from WFDU General Manager, Kenny O'Boyle
Hello everyone!
I hope you and your loved ones are safe, healthy and managing okay during these unprecedented times.
I wanted to give you all an update, but unfortunately there is not much to update you on. The question I get more than any other from our staff and listeners is, “When will WFDU be able to resume normal, live programming?” Unfortunately, I do not have an answer to this question. Logically, I would have to assume that WFDU Staff will not be allowed back inside the station until the government stay at home restrictions are lifted. Who knows when that will be? Even when those restrictions are lifted, it’s still ultimately up to the university.
What can we do and what are we doing?
We can stay on the air and streaming
We can keep the RetroRadio Oldies coming Monday through Friday on HD1
We can broadcast recorded messages from our RetroRadio hosts and we are experimenting with ways to broadcast live remotely and even take listener requests (stay tuned)
HD1 weekend shows have been submitting new material and recordings of past shows and they have been airing consistently
We are now accepting new material and recordings of past shows for our programs on HD2 and will begin airing those ASAP
I speak on behalf of the entire staff and I’m sure many of you too when I say we all can’t wait to return to normal. We all miss doing our shows and most of all, interacting with you! Please be patient. We all have to be.
I very much appreciate all of the listeners that have reached out via email, phone or Facebook. Overwhelmingly, the messages are positive and appreciative that WFDU is still on the air even in this limited capacity. It warms my heart to hear that WFDU can be a source of comfort during all of this.
If you would like to reach out with any comments, questions or concerns, please do.
Phone: 201-692-2806 (Leave a message)
Email: wfdu@fdu.edu
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/WFDURADIO/
Keep listening and thanks for supporting WFDU!
- Kenny
